<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Chloe Veigel&#39;s Github Site</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Chloe Veigel&#39;s Github Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Can Alabama Football End Up Back On Top in 2022?</title>
      <link>/2022/04/22/can-alabama-end-up-back-on-top-in-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/04/22/can-alabama-end-up-back-on-top-in-2022/</guid>
      <description>Alabama football has continuously been a team that shows up and shows out year after year. They continue to get players that know how to play the game and that dominate the field.
In the past ten years, the Alabama Crimson Tide have taken the College Football National Championship title four times. But this past year, Georgia beat them in a tough battle. Can Alabama manage to get back on top in 2022?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adrian Martinez left Nebraska.. for better or for worse?</title>
      <link>/2022/04/01/adrian-martinez/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/04/01/adrian-martinez/</guid>
      <description>For the past couple of years, Nebraska fans have had a love/hate relationship with their football team. Since Scott Frost came on as Head Coach in 2018, the Huskers have achieved a total of 15 wins and, prepare yourself, a total of 29 losses.
With 2021 being another rocky season for Nebraska football, the quarterback, Adrian Martinez, was on the front lines of the hate being received. He has now transferred to play at Kansas State, making many Husker fans appreciative, but was he really the issue?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
